https://millward.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyAt The Millward Partnership Ltd we take the privacy of our users very seriously. We are committed to maintaining the security, privacy and confidentiality of all users and visitors to this site. This Privacy Statement explains our data practices. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our practices please contact our web site supervisor by email at info@Millward.co.ukIn order to assist you and provide services we must collect information on you and we are governed by The General Data Protection Regulations in how this data may be collected, stored and utilised. This information may be collected through email or other correspondence or verbal instructions.Personal information is collected and used for the purposes of marketing only. This data assists us in personalising the services we provide.Information is collected from users accessing this website. This may include browsing patterns or other data automatically collected.If you decide to provide your personal details for the purposes of obtaining further information you may be asked to provide details such as your name, address and email address.You may request a copy of the information we hold on you (a Subject Access Request) by contacting us in writing at 1 Malin Hill, Nottingham, NG1 1JQ and addressing your request to the GDPR Administrator.This Privacy Statement does not apply to third party internet sites to which a link is available from this site.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you accept this.I AcceptCookie Policy
